但有时你可以做，哦，天哪，我需要拯救它，或者如果我拯救它，或者粉丝，或者......它会在你的脑海中浮现，你知道吗？
But sometimes you can do, oh, my God, I need to save it, or if I save it, or the fans, or... And it goes through your mind, you know?
这就是我的问题。
That's my question.
你如何处理这些想法？
How do you deal with these thoughts?
罢工的那一刻就是我说，好吧，
The moment of the strike is when I say, OK,
这是我的时刻。
This is my moment.
我只需要专注于我自己。
I need to focus only on myself.
杰出的。
Brilliant.
哦，寒冷，伙计。
Oh, chilly, mate.
真的非常非常冷。
It's really, really cold.
在这个国家已经 12 年了，对我来说太冷了。
It's been 12 years in this country and too freezing for me.
我在比赛之间有一点休息时间，所以我会在点球大战中做一些工作
I've got a little break between games so I'm going to work a little bit on penalties
在心理方面，当你成功赢得大型锦标赛的比赛时，总是知道自己的表现是件好事
and mental side it's good to always you know when you when you're successful winning tournaments big tournaments
因此，不断尝试并提高自己是件好事。
So it's good to keep trying and improve yourself.
这对我来说是一个重要的时刻。
It's a big moment for me.
我总觉得这是一个机会
I always feel like it's an opportunity to
闪耀并展示我有多优秀，我在点球大战中有多强。
to shine and to show how good I am, how strong I am in penalties.
我从没想过我会成为英雄。
I never think I'm gonna be the hero.
你知道，这只是享受这一刻。
It's just about, you know, enjoying the moment.
从很小的时候起。
since a very young age.
从我记事起，大概七、八次，我在点球大战中一直很幸运，你知道。
Since I remember, probably seven, eight, I've always been lucky in penalty shootouts, you know.
赢的比输的多。
win more than lose.
当你年轻的时候，你只是为了快乐而玩耍。
When you're young, you just play for joy.
你知道，当你年纪大了，
You know, when you're older,
你为球队效力，为俱乐部效力，所以你需要以不同的方式表现。
You play for a team, you play for a club, so you need to perform in a different way.
很难进入每个守门员的脑海，但有时守门员，当你进入点球大战时，
It's hard to go to every goalie's mind, but sometimes goalies, when you go to a penalty shootout,
他们可以给自己一点压力，想，哦，如果你不接受，那么每个人都会看着我......
they can have a little bit of pressure on themselves, thinking, oh, if you don't take one, then everyone will look at me and...
他们会认为我打了一场糟糕的比赛或者我不够好。
and they would think I had a bad game or I'm not good enough.
是的，很高兴听到。
Yeah, good to hear.
埃米还是吉布提？
Emi or Djibouti?
艾米，艾米很好。
Emi, Emi is fine.
是的，欧洲或妈妈。
Yeah, Europe or Mami.
如果你来这里，让我快速向你解释一下。
If you come over here, let me explain it to you real quick.
这是你的大脑活动。
This is your brain activity right here.
然后我们会看到不同的大脑状态，我们试图帮助您更好地进入该区域。
and then we see the different brain states and what we are trying to help you with is to better get into the zone.
所以当你处于最佳的大脑状态时，声音就会从扬声器中播放出来，就在这里，
So when you're in that optimal brain state, then the sound will play from the speaker, this one right here,
这将表明您现在管理压力的能力以及注意力的集中程度。
And this will indicate how well you're managing pressure and how well focused you are right now.
那么 Emi，你能介绍一下你的日常工作并解释一下你在游戏中会做什么吗？
So Emi, can you go through your routine and just explain a little bit what you would do in the game, please?
我从一边移动到另一边。
I move side to side.
我只需要一点点就能把火点燃。
It's just a bit for me to get that fire up.
有时快，有时慢，取决于我白天的感受。
Sometimes quicker, sometimes slower, depends how I feel during the day.
然后当它快要罢工的时候，
And then when it's about to strike,
当你想，好吧，我不想早去，因为他们在等你。
is when you think, OK, I don't want to go early, because they wait for you.
他们还在看着你。
They're still looking at you.
他们现在非常聪明，所以这是关于
They're very clever nowadays, so it's about
稍微移动一下，不让他们看到我要走的路。
moving a little bit to not show them any sign of which way I'm going.
然后在最后一刻开火，你知道，因为如果我去那里，在他即将攻击的那一刻，他就看到了我，所以他们会这么说。
and then fire at the last minute, you know, because if I'm going there, by the moment he's about to strike, he sees me, so they would put it that way.
确保我的双腿不要张得过大，以致无法准备好推动。
Make sure I don't open my legs too wide to be ready to push.
首先，我们要对这边进行处罚。
First, we're going to do penalties towards this side.
五于此。
Five to this.
然后我们将在任一方向进行五个。
Then we'll do five either direction.
你不知道是哪一边。
You don't know which side.
然后我们随机进行五个。
And then we do five random.
还记得声音吗？
Remember the sound?
是的。
Yeah.
好吧，就是这个模式。
OK, so it's this mode.
当我说专注时，就是当你专注并且你变得清晰的时候。
When I say focus, that's when you focus and you get clear.
你知道我的意思？
You know what I mean?
所以我们从前五个开始。
So we start with the first five.
重点。
Focus.
好的。
Okay, good.
Nice.
不错，不错。
Nice, good.
好吧，还有三个。
All right, three more.
重点。
Focus.
不错，很棒。
Nice, great.
好的。
Nice.
当你有这种流畅的动作时，例如在世界杯上，它真的很流畅。
When you have this fluid motion that you had, for example, at the World Cup, it was really fluid.
时机非常完美。
The timing was perfect.
这就是你安排时间的时候。
That's when you make, say, timing.
定时。
Timing.
你有到达那里的压力，对吗？
You have the pressure of getting there, right?
因为如果你基本上持有这手牌，那么你保存它的机会就更高，对吗？
Because if you're basically here with the hand, it's a higher chance of you saving it, right?
这就是为什么你真正将负压力视为可以限制你的东西。
So that's why you really extend negative pressure as something that can limit you.
发挥出最佳状态。
to perform at your best.
因此，如果你的动作不流畅，它也会限制你跳跃的距离。
So it can also limit you from jumping as far if your movement is not fluid.
这就是为什么你想要真正集中注意力以达到最远的距离并获得最高的扑救百分比。
So that's why you want to really be optimally focused to get to the furthest distance and have the highest percentage of saving a penalty.
正是这种信心让你能够应对压力。
And it's that confidence that makes you deal with that pressure.
如果你不确定要去哪里并且在跑步过程中改变了主意，
If you're not sure where you're going to go and you change your mind during the run,
就是这样。
That's it.
你不这么说。
You don't say that.
有些守门员，你知道他什么时候跑动。
Some of the goalies, you know when he's running.
他们不断变化，哦，西方正在走向低、高、中。
They keep changing, oh, West is going low, high, mid.
我选择一侧。
I'm choosing one side.
我不认为他会走向中低位。
I'm not thinking he's going mid, low.
直到我认为事情进展顺利。
until I think it is going right.
我的意思是，准备工作是应对压力的一部分，对吧？
And I mean, that's part of dealing with the pressure is the preparation, right?
是的，但是世界杯的准备，决赛，
Yeah, but the preparation in the World Cup, in the final,
梅西告诉我他的腿很高。
Messi told me that he was going legs high.
所以我做好了准备。
So I prepared myself.
身体形状，是的，它正在那里。
The body shape, yeah, it's going there.
但随后我向右俯冲，球的高度变低了。
But then I dive right, the height, and the ball went low.
所以我的准备就是要走高，然后在那一刻，
So my preparation was to go high, then in the moment,
变低了，所以我也更注重我的直觉。
went low, so I'm more about my intuition as well.
我知道统计数据是正确的。
I know it's true about the stats.
只需阅读此时此刻您面前的内容即可。
Just read what's in front of you at the moment.
哦。
Oh.
打击还是不错的
Good strike still.
例如，当你要投篮时，比方说，前四分得分，而第五分的压力来了，你如何应对？
When, for example, you're going to shoot out, let's say, the first four score, and the pressure comes for the fifth, how do you deal with that?
首先你需要相信自己，你知道吗？
The first thing you need to believe in yourself, you know?
不再分散他们的注意力或试图进入他们的头脑。
No more distracting them or trying to go into their head.
我想更多的是
I think more about
我的时机，你知道，我的步法。
my timing, you know, my footwork.
比方说，如果你猜到了侧面，
Let's say, if you guessed the side,
然后你不保存它，然后它就关闭了。
then you don't save it, then it's off.
你知道，你会感到不安，但你正在做一件好事，那就是猜测网站。
You know, you get upset, but you're doing something good, which is guessing the site.
然后问题是当
And then the problem is when
这是点球大战。
It's a penalty shootout.
而你根本就没有走，你会想，哦，这不是我的日子，你知道吗？
and you go nowhere near, you think, oh, it's not my day, you know?
但我总是想，我总是说一个。
But I always think, I always say one.
你知道，我本可以轻松救两个人。
You know, I could have saved two easily.
你知道，在五分钟内，你救了两个，你就赢了。
You know, in five, you save two, you win.
我的机会越来越少了，你知道的。
I've got less chances, you know.
哦！
Oh!
自从你进去之后你的身体形状，100%。
Your body shape since you go in there, 100%.
你做？
You do?
是的。
Yeah.
你能具体说明一下吗？
Can you specify that a little bit?
他的身形，他的手贴在他的身上。
His body shape, his hand is stuck to his body.
你知道，当他过马路时，他的拇指会多留一点。
You know, when he's going across, he leaves his thumb a little bit more.
但这一手，他却留了下来。
But this one, he kept the hands.
离他很近，所以我知道他会朝那个方向走。
close to him, so I knew he was going that way.
杰出的。
Brilliant.
你的重点非常非常明确。
Your focus was very, very clear.
这就是为什么我什至在你的眼中注意到了这一点。
And that's why I even noticed it in your eyes.
在你眼里，现在你很兴奋。
In your eyes, now you're excited.
现在是你喜欢的部分了。
Now it's the part that you love.
好吧，最后一张，最后一张。
All right, last one, last one.
我们走吧。
Let's go.
重点。
Focus.
他现在做了一些不同的事情。
He's done something different now.
因为他不想让我看到他的体型。
Because he doesn't want to show me the body shape.
你看，不是吗？
You see, no?
他正在接近你。
He's getting to you.
你做你的事。
You do your thing.
事情进展得很艰难。
It's going hard.
你有没有看到？
Did you see?
肮脏的。
Dirty.
我们现在要研究数据。
We're going to look into the data now.
首先，你需要适当的挑战。
First of all, you need a proper challenge.
对你来说，如果你的活力不足，
For you, it's like, if you're under-activated,
没有必要这样做。
There's no point to do it.
是的，这很正常。
Yeah, it's normal.
一直都是这样吗？
Was that always like that?
这就是我向你提出的问题。
That's my question to you.
你觉得，因为这是一个性格问题，这是一个个性的答案，对吗？
Were you like, because it's a character thing, it's a personality answer, right?
是的。
Yeah.
不不，我需要挑战，是的。
No, no, I need to challenge, yeah.
我需要有人给你动力，给你动力，给你感觉。
I need someone to wind you up, to fire you up, to give you feel.
因为我觉得非常有趣的一件事是，你在这个区域的比例提高了 85%
Because the one thing I find really interesting, you're 85% more in the zone
当它去往任何地方（与左或右相比）时。
when it goes anywhere compared to left or right.
当挑战真的很高时，你实际上会更投入。
When the challenge is really high, you're actually more in the zone.
我发现这实际上非常令人着迷，因为它确实代表了
And I find that actually quite fascinating, you know, because it really represents
个性和你的行为方式之类的东西。
personality and the way you act and this kind of stuff.
是的，这让我更舒服。
Yeah, it makes me more comfortable.
确实如此，是的。
It does, yeah.
我打球是为了兴奋并失去所有的紧张。
I play to be fired up and to lose all my nerves.
但有时你可以做，哦，天哪，我需要拯救它，或者如果我拯救它，或者粉丝，或者......它会在你的脑海中浮现，你知道吗？
But sometimes you can do, oh, my God, I need to save it, or if I save it, or the fans, or... And it goes through your mind, you know?
问我一个问题，你如何处理这些想法？
Ask my question, how do you deal with these thoughts?
罢工的那一刻就是我说，好吧，这是我的时刻。
The moment of the strike is when I say, OK, this is my moment.
我只需要专注于自己，你知道吗？
I need to focus only on myself, you know?
好吧，那一刻就像关机一样。
Okay, so in that moment it's like switch off.
关掉电源后，我就会对着球对抗他，而不是对抗，你知道。
Switch off and it's me against the ball against him, not against, you know.
30亿人通过电视观看世界杯决赛。
3 billion people watching on the TV in the World Cup finals.
就这么简单。
It's as simple as that.
你知道，我曾经说过，
You know, I used to say,
发送点球信息以获得信心，但我无法挽救任何东西
message to shoot penalty to to get that confidence and i can't save anything
所以这没有帮助。
So it doesn't help.
这没有帮助。
It doesn't help.
为了你对我的信任，所以我知道的其实并不多，好吧，我都懂了
for your confidence for me so i know not practically too much okay i got it all right
非常感谢，非常感谢。
Thank you so much, appreciate it.
这是一种乐趣。
It was a pleasure.
嗯，我们发现的一件事是
Well, one thing we found was that
他确实需要挑战。
He really needs the challenge.
因此，他实际上随着焦点的增加而增加。
So with that, he increases actually with the focus.
这非常令人着迷。
It's quite fascinating.
我认为当我更加专注并且压力很大并且我更加专注时，我得到了 85%
I got 85% I think when I'm more in the zone and the pressure is there and I focus more
当压力来临时，这很有趣，你知道，这就是
when the pressure's on, which is interesting, you know, and that's something that
你知道，我在压力区所做的就是我发挥最好的时候。
that I do, you know, in the pressure zone is when I play the best.
当你是一名年轻的门将时，你会倾听俱乐部的意见，并尽力为俱乐部做一切。
When you're a young goalkeeper, you listen to what the club says and you try to do everything for the club.
但有时你需要倾听自己的声音并跟随自己的直觉。
but sometimes you need to listen to yourself and just follow your gut.
并承担风险。
and take risks.
如果你不冒险，你就不会获得丰厚的回报。
If you don't take the risk, you won't have big rewards.
你必须投入你的努力、你的技术、你的心理准备，所有这些东西，然后你就尽你最大的努力。
You have to put in your hard work, your technique, your mental preparation, all these kinds of things, and then you just give it your best shot.
如果所有这些事情加在一起，
And if all those things come together,
这就像一个谜题。
That's like a puzzle.
重点。
Focus.
当有那么大的压力时，我真的很喜欢它，因为我总是认为这是一场游戏。
When there's that amount of pressure, I really enjoy it because I always think it's a game.
归根结底，这只是足球，所以你可以赢也可以输。
At the end of the day, it's just football, so you can win or lose.
但玩得开心总是好的。
But it's always good to have fun.
谢谢。
Thank you.